{
    "id": "334ac5cb7833427fa0269db3804c1080",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Give me something to drink, or …………….. I will die of thirst.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "else",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a027bcc9a66f4e018fddd388e1dab8cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. you are mistaken or I am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9140971a023e42b0bdd4d8ed3b727d8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked …………………. he might have something to eat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "weather",
                "whether",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "73ce54606d5f43ac9f6601f869577bae"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you are called, you must come in at once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "While"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c185fc1da199427fa3636a3ad44761ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "I cannot give you any money ………………. I have none.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "that",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3b796c7b3dd04736a6786b202f62712a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not succeed ………………. you work harder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "weather"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61501c817ce040f98bb08ff34a20dd83"
        },
        {
            "question": "He fled ………………. he should be killed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "lest",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c87fbe0f821a4237acd337bc5c0aae89"
        },
        {
            "question": "We started early ………………… we will not get stuck in the traffic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "such that",
                "such as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cfb3f36a438c4413bca3139373c1c022"
        },
        {
            "question": "He deserves to succeed …………….. he works hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c8b0b732ce42469a9e4586f46be5a713"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hear ………………… your brother is in China.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8df26261e0974572891b2a89cfe737ab"
        }
    ]
}